Right now, the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, is at the prayer line of the Colombia Crusade,
and God Almighty is using him to pray for the sick and afflicted,
setting them free from every bondage in their lives.
Prayer Line At The Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
As the resurrection power of Jesus Christ moves through Prophet T.B. Joshua,
demons in the lives of people begin to manifest and cry out.
Who are you?
Shut up!
It is not your business!
Leave me!
Prayer Line At The Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
What's your business?
Leave me alone!
Prayer Line At The Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua - Day 1
What's your business?
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Set Free In Jesus' Name
She is free.
CRUSADE WITH T.B. JOSHUA, Cali, Colombia
TESTIMONY TIME
Miss Leidy Dominguez - Cali, Colombia
Her name is Leidy Dominguez, and she comes from Cali, Colombia.
First of all, I was suffering from an eating disorder and was self-harming.
I was aggressive and got angry all the time amongst other problems.
This was what I went through every day.
She said, in her daily life, she was always angry.
She had an eating disorder.
I mainly came because of my sister
but when I felt the presence of the man of God close to me,
I started to get desperate and when he touched me, I started running.
I began to scream out of desperation and wanted to start hurting myself.
First of all, I came here because of my sister
but when the prophet came towards her,
she started to feel anxiety; she started to run, scream and hit herself.
After Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you, how do you now feel?
I felt so calm and peaceful.
I came with so many burdens of stress and anger but now everything has gone.
Now, I have peace.
She said, she feels at peace and calm.
She feels that any problem she had with anger is in the past right now.
How did you hear about today's miracle crusade with Prophet T.B. Joshua?
I heard about the crusade on social networks.
I first learnt about it through my aunt who attends a church here in Cali.
She informed us and we confirmed from the social networks that it was true.
As soon as I knew about it, I went to register my sister for the crusade.
She said, one of her aunts came to invite her.
Because of that, she started to look for more information on the internet, social media.
Because of that, she wanted to bring her sister to this miracle crusade.
What is your advice to all the youth out there
that are suffering with the same problems that you had in the past
such as eating disorders and anger problems?
Testimony From Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
You simply have to look for God because God is love and peace.
Things like anger, rage, burdens and eating disorders don't come from God.
They came from demons - the enemy who always wants to destroy us.
Her advice is that people have to look for God
because God is love and peace.
Any problems like anger and eating disorders come from the devil.
Don't be stubborn; if you are delivered, it is because God is working in your life and He is calling you.
I am speaking from my experience; I have been stubborn many times.
That was why the devil could always find an opportunity to enter my life.
She said, we have to be close to God.
We thank God for your deliverance today.
It is not enough to just seek deliverance but it is also important to maintain your deliverance
by staying close to Jesus.
Testimony From Colombia Crusade With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Thank you very much. I just love God; He is great!
Thank you very much. God is great!
Jesus is great!
He alone is my Father!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.